Creating personas in marketing,
لإنشاء الشخصيات في التسويق،
you just imagine what Becky would like and what she wears,
عليك تخيل ما قد تحبه "بيكي" وما ترتديه
and where she shops, and why she would want to be a customer of your company.
وأين تتسوق ولماذا ستريد أن تكون زبونة لشركتك.
The way that we do it is we actually take real lead files from the client.
طريقتنا لفعل ذلك هي بأخذ ملفات معلومات حقيقية من العميل المستهدف.
We do analysis using LinkedIn data.
ونقوم بالتحليل باستخدام بيانات منصة LinkedIn.
This is their age, this is their title.
هذه أعمارهم وهذه هي مسمياتهم الوظيفية.
We create personas for the client that are based on real data.
ونصنع شخصيات للعميل بناء على بيانات فعلية.
My name is Emily Peters.
اسمي "إميلي بيترز".
I'm a brand strategist and I'm founder of Uncommon Bold.
أنا خبيرة استراتيجيات العلامات تجارية ومؤسسة شركة Uncommon Bold.
Uncommon Bold is a brand strategy studio.
Uncommon Bold هي ستوديو لوضع استراتيجيات العلامات التجارية.
We help companies when they feel like they're misunderstood.
نساعد الشركات عندما يرون أنه قد تمت إساءة فهمهم.
We do a bunch of analysis and then we help them to choose
حيث نقوم بعدة تحليلات ومن ثم نساعدهم على اختيار الدرب الذي يريدون سلكه،
really compelling and is going to help them get a ton of VC money,
ويكون جذاباً ويساعدهم على استقطاب الكثير من أموال رأس المال الاستثماري
a ton of press, a ton of people to join their company.
والكثير من الاهتمام الإعلامي ولينضم إلى شركاتهم الكثير من الناس.
My clients are all doctors and scientists and engineers,
إن جميع زبائني هم أطباء وعلماء ومهندسون،
and they all think in data.
وجميعهم يعتمدون على البيانات في كل شيء.
The way I do a very detailed data analysis with
الطريقة التي أتبعها هي بالقيام تحليل بيانات مفصل جداً
media coverage for my clients to give them a sense of the quality of the coverage,
مع التغطية الإعلامية لعملائي لإعطائهم حساً بجودة التغطية،
not just the quantity they're receiving.
وليس فقط الكم الذي يتلقونه.
So we created an algorithm, really simple,
لذلك قمنا بإنشاء خوارزمية بسيطة
that helps to show,
تساعد على عرض
create a score that they can measure month over month to see how they're doing.
وخلق نتائج يمكنهم قياسها شهراً بعد شهر للتحقق من أدائهم.
When I first developed that,
عندما قمت بتطوير هذا في البداية
it was pretty transformational to have this very simple formula that was very
كان أمراً ثورياً امتلاك معادلة بسيطة سهلة الفهم
I actually posted it on my website and a lot of other people use it now.
لقد قمت في الواقع بنشرها على موقعي، ويقوم الآن العديد من الأشخاص باستخدامها.
So that's nice to know that I'm helping
إنه لأمر جميل معرفة أني أساعد
other people to demonstrate the value of their work.
أناساً أخرين في إظهار قيمة أعمالهم.
Everything needs to be managed and measured.
على كل شيء أن يتم إدارته وقياسه.
With data, you can actually go back and look at the numbers,
يمكنك باستخدام البيانات العودة ومراجعة الأرقام
look at the traction,
والعملاؤ الذين تم استقطابهم.
you can really get in there with a client and have tough conversations with them
يمكنك حقاً التفاعل مع العميل وخوض محادثة جدية وصارمة معهم،
because of using real information versus just opinion.
لأننا نستخدم معلومات فعلية بدلاً من مجرد آراء.
You can get pretty far in your career without data.
يمكنك تحقيق الكثير في مسيرتك المهنية من دون البيانات.
But, if you have a good sense of how to put
ولكن إن كان لديك فكرة عن كيفية
together a compelling slide or a compelling graph,
إنشاء شريحة عرض أو رسم بياني جذاب،
it elevates your ability to really convince
فسيزيد ذلك من قدرتك على إقناع الناس باتخاذ الإجراءات التي ترغب فيها.